{
    "translations": {
      "en": {
        "q2": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "We will construct an algorithm to convert any Right Linear grammar to a Left Linear grammar.",
          "question":"[T|F] finding an algorithm to convert Right Regular Grammar (RRG) to Left Regular Grammar(LRG) means that we proved that any RRG has LRG.",
          "answer": "True",
          "choices": ["True", "False"]
        },
        "q3": {
            "type": "select",
            "description": "During the construction of the algorithm, we will convert the following grammr to Left Linear Grammar.",
            "question":"What is L(G)",
            "answer": ["$a^*cbb^*$", "$\\{a^ncb^m \\mid n\\ge 0, m>0\\}$"],
            "choices": ["$a^*cbb^*$", "$\\{a^ncb^m \\mid n\\ge 0, m>0\\}$"]
          },
          "q4": {
            "type": "multiple",
            "description": "Since the Language $L$ has a Right Linear grammar, we can follow ``NFA from Regular Grammar'' proof in the previous modules to construct an NFA for the language.",
            "question":"What does it mean to follow ``NFA from Regular Grammar'' prrof?",
            "answer": "Convert Regular Grammar to NFA",
            "choices": ["Convert NFA to Regular grammar", "Convert Regular Grammar to NFA"]
          },
          "q11": {
            "type": "select",
            "description": "The next step in our algorithm is to REVERSE the NFA.",
            "question":"How can we reverse an NFA?",
            "answer": ["This means that we need to filp all transitions", "Swap the start and final states"],
            "choices": ["This means that we need to filp all transitions", "Swap the start and final states"]
          },
          "q12": {
            "type": "select",
            "description": "Lest us start by reversing the transitions.",
            "question":"What is the result of reversing the transitions $\\delta(S, a) = S$, and $\\delta(A, b) = A$?",
            "answer": ["The edge that represent $\\delta(S, a) = S$ will not change as it is a loop.", "The edge that represent $\\delta(A, b) = A$ will not change as it is a loop."],
            "choices": ["The edge that represent $\\delta(S, a) = S$ will not change as it is a loop.", "The edge that represent $\\delta(A, b) = A$ will not change as it is a loop."]
          },
          "q13": {
            "type": "multiple",
            "description": "Lest us start by reversing the transitions.",
            "question":"What is the result of reversing the transition $\\delta(S, c) = A$?",
            "answer": "$\\delta(A, c) = S$",
            "choices": ["$\\delta(S, a) = S$", "$\\delta(A, b) = A$", "$\\delta(A, c) = S$", "$\\delta(S, c) = A$", "$\\delta(A, b) = F$", "$\\delta(F, b) = A$"]
          },
          "q14": {
            "type": "multiple",
            "description": "Lest us start by reversing the transitions.",
            "question":"What is the result of reversing the transition $\\delta(A, b) = F$?",
            "answer": "$\\delta(F, b) = A$",
            "choices": ["$\\delta(S, a) = S$", "$\\delta(A, b) = A$", "$\\delta(A, c) = S$", "$\\delta(S, c) = A$", "$\\delta(A, b) = F$", "$\\delta(F, b) = A$"]
          },
          "q15": {
            "type": "multiple",
            "description": "All edges are reversed.",
            "question":"What is the next step?",
            "answer": "Swap the start and Final states",
            "choices": ["Done, the NFA is reversed.", "Swap the start and Final states"]
          },
          "q17": {
            "type": "multiple",
            "description": "Convert the final state to be the initital state.",
            "question":"In case that the NFA has multiple final states. How can we convert them to a start state?",
            "answer": "Convert the NFA with multiple final states to an NFA with one final state. Then make the new final state a start state.",
            "choices": ["Convert every final state to a start state", "Convert the NFA with multiple final states to an NFA with one final state. Then make the new final state a start state."]
          },
          "q19": {
            "type": "multiple",
            "description": "We can follow the ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof from the slides to get the right linear grammar for $NFA_{rev}$. Thus, we have the right linear grammar for $L^R$.",
            "question":"What does it mean to follow ``RR Grammar from DFA'' prrof?",
            "answer": "Convert NFA to Regular grammar",
            "choices": ["Convert NFA to Regular grammar", "Convert Regular Grammar to NFA"]
          },
          "q20": {
            "type": "multiple",
            "description": "We can follow the ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof from the slides to get the right linear grammar for $NFA_{rev}$. Thus, we have the right linear grammar for $L^R$.",
            "question":"What is the production equivelent to the transition $\\delta(S, a) = S$?",
            "answer": "$S\\rightarrow aS$",
            "choices": ["$S\\rightarrow aS$", "$S\\rightarrow Sa$"]
          },
          "q21": {
            "type": "multiple",
            "description": "We can follow the ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof from the slides to get the right linear grammar for $NFA_{rev}$. Thus, we have the right linear grammar for $L^R$.",
            "question":"What is the production equivelent to the transition $\\delta(A, b) = A$?",
            "answer": "$A\\rightarrow bA$",
            "choices": ["$A\\rightarrow bA$", "$A\\rightarrow Ab$"]
          },
          "q22": {
            "type": "multiple",
            "description": "We can follow the ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof from the slides to get the right linear grammar for $NFA_{rev}$. Thus, we have the right linear grammar for $L^R$.",
            "question":"What is the production equivelent to the transition $\\delta(A, c) = S$?",
            "answer": "$A\\rightarrow cS$",
            "choices": ["$A\\rightarrow Sc$", "$A\\rightarrow cS$"]
          },
          "q23": {
            "type": "multiple",
            "description": "We can follow the ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof from the slides to get the right linear grammar for $NFA_{rev}$. Thus, we have the right linear grammar for $L^R$.",
            "question":"What is the production equivelent to the transition $\\delta(F, b) = A$?",
            "answer": "$F\\rightarrow cA$",
            "choices": ["$F\\rightarrow cA$", "$F\\rightarrow Ac$"]
          },
          "q24": {
            "type": "multiple",
            "description": "We can follow the ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof from the slides to get the right linear grammar for $NFA_{rev}$. Thus, we have the right linear grammar for $L^R$.",
            "question":"What is the production equivelent to the transition ?",
            "answer": "$F\\rightarrow cA$",
            "choices": ["$F\\rightarrow cA$", "$F\\rightarrow Ac$"]
          }
    }
  }
}
    